Norton, Joseph L.; Papers ua902.006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1946-ca. 1996, Undated; 4; 5.4 cubic ft.
  - Reference Material, 1946-1991, Undated; 4.3; 4.3 cubic ft.
    - Exceptional Children, 1954; 1955; 1958-1962 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Explaining Test Results to Parents, 1959; 1961 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Fifth Freedom, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - A Frog is a Frog, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - G.E. Career Brochures, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Gay Academics Union Newsletter, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Gay Athletics, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Bay Bibliography, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - The Gay Clone, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Gay Counceling Publications, 1973; 1974; 1978; 1979; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Gay Images, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Gay & Lesbian Youth, 1991; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Gay Lifestyle Test, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Gay Light, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - "Gay Male Fantasies and Realities", 1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Gay Rights Platform in the United States, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Gay Self-Esteem, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Gay Support Project, 1976-1983 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Gay Teachers, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - GPU News, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Graduate Faculty Interested in Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1984 July (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Grassroots, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Richard Green Article on Gender Identity, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Grief in Children, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Group Guidance, 1955; 1962-1968 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Group Procedures Newsletter, 1969 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Group Processes, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Guidance, 1962-1966; 1977 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Guidance in Schools, 1954; 1957-1958; 1964; 1968-1969; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Guliford Interview, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Happiness, 1963 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - High School Guidance, 1962; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - High School Psychology, 1959 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - History of Counseling - New York State, 1953; 1959; 1963; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Homophobia, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Homosexual Counseling Journal, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Homosexuality, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Homosexuality and Health, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - Homosexuality and Mental Health, 1973-1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - Human Sexuality, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - Human Sexuality, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - Humanist Association, 1962-1967 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Identity Formation, Rights and Needs, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Impact Program Brochures, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Implosive Therapy, 1967 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Individual Counseling, 1972-1974 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Job Analysis of Directors of Guidance, 1955 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Job Satisfaction, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Journal of Homosexuality, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Junior High Guidance, 1957; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Keeping up with Youth, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - League of Emotionally Disturbed Children, 1957 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Legal Aspects of Transexualism, 1973; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Legal and Philosophical Concepts of Certification, 1967 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Legal and Social Interface, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Legal Status of Insanity, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Lesbian and Gay Gerontologists, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Lesbians Rising, 1979 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - "Loving Someone Gay" workshop announcement and book list, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Making Visible Syllabus, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Male Adolescent Prostitution, 1979 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Maslow Papers, 1955-1956 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - McWhirter and Mattison talk, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Meditation, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Mental Health and Gay Population, 1972; 1979 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Mental Health Newsletters, 1962-1964 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Mental Health - pamphlets, brochures, 1954; 1956; 1958-1961; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Most Important Psychologists Study, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Motivation and Overachievers, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Norman C. Murphy affidavit, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - National Conference of Pupil Personnel Services, 1971 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Needs Theory, 1961 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Non-Disrimination Companies, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - NEA Journal, 1960 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - New York State Conference for Gay & Lesbian Rights - proposed by-laws, 1980 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - New York State Court Decision - Ron Onofre, 1980 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Newspaper Articles about Joseph Norton, 1975; 1984; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - NGA Bulletin, 1983 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Notes on Education, 1976; 1979; 1981 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Notes on Homosexuality, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Notes and materials on homophobia, 1971; 1983; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Notes and materials on homophobia, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Occupational Aspiration Scale, 1963; 1966; 1967; 1968; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Occupational Monograph, 1970; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - On the Job, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Overtricks Bridge Club, 1986 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Paraprofessionals, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Personal Orientation Inventory, 1969 March (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Personality notes, perception & sleep, 1966 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Photograph - view from Table Mountain, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - Piercing, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Planned Parenthood of Albany, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Planning Marital Critique, 1968 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Play Therapy bibliography, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Poetry, 1959 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Population Project, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - Potsdam-Canton Gay Community, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - Practicum, 1972; 1976 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - Practicum Supervision, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - Preparation of School Counselors, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Privacy, 1967; 1971 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Projective Techniques, 1947; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Psychology of Aging, 1946; 1951-1953; 1958-1959; 1961-1962; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - Publications - Gay Rights, 1970-1979 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - Publications - Various, 1976; 1977; 1980 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 64)
    - Pupil Personnel Services, 1963; 1964 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 65)
    - Quality of Life, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 66)
    - Quotes on Homosexuality, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 67)
    - Rape Information, 1979; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 68)
    - Reality Therapy, 1965 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 69)
    - Recordkeeping Policies for Students, 1969 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 70)
    - Redefining Deviance, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 71)
    - Referral Psychologists, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 72)
    - Referral Services, 1967 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 73)
    - Religion and Homosexuality, 1973-1975 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 74)
    - Religious aspoects of Transsexualism, 1978; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 75)
    - Research on Aptitude Tests, 1955 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 76)
    - Resident Assistant Apprenticeship Program, 1971 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 77)
    - Resources for Youth Newsletter, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 78)
    - Response to Clark Bell, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 79)
    - Rice Repertory Test, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 80)
    - S&M (Sadomasochism), 1976; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - The School to Employment Program, 1963 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - School Psychologists, 1961 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Self-Actualization, Maslow, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - The Self-Directed Search, 1978 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Self-Study, 1978 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Self Test, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Sex Counseling, 1976; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Sex Education, 1960-1977 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Sex Education, 1960-1977 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Sex Education, 1964-1967 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Sex Education, 1965-1967; 1975 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Sex Education, 1966-1979 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Sex Education, 1975-1978; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Sex Education, 1978; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Sex Education, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Sex Education, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Sex Education - clippings, 1966; 1967; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Sex Education - curricula, 1967-1968 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Sex Equality in Guidance Opportunities, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Sex and the Handicapped, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Sex Role Expectations, 1979 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Sex Talk, 1968; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Sex Therapy, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Sexual Health Knowledge Surveys, 1972-1976 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Sexual History Interview, 1980 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Sexuality Today, 1977-12-1980-06 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Sexuality Today, 1980-07-1982-02 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - SIECUS Report, 1976-1981 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Some Points to Work into a talk on homosexuality, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Song of Remembrance by Shannon Stein, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Special Education, 1964 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - State Control of Education, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Student Personnel Papers, 1971 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Stuttering Paper by Barbara Scouler, 1955 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Suicide Among Young Adults, 1957; 1973 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - SUNYA Gay Alliance Statement, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - The Syracuse Sun, 1972-06 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Systematic Counseling, 1967-1971 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Test Service Bulletin, 1948-1959 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - TGIC News, 1991 July-1991 August; Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Training in Business and Industry, 1966 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Transgender Issues - notes, reference materials, correspondence, 1976; 1980; 1982; 2000; Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - The Transgenderist, 1992; 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - The Transgenderist, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - The Transgenderist, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - The Transgenderist, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - The Transgenderist, 1997 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - The Transgenderist, 1998 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Underachievement bibliography, 1960-1963 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - UUP Solidarity Committee, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Vocational Analysis Research, 1966 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Vocational Survey Research, 1950; 1968 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - What Do We Really Know about Career Development?, 1970 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Edward J. Wheeler, 1963; 1964; 1966 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - West Side Gay Theatre, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Woman: Myth and Reality, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Women and Aging, 1978 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)